In this section, we learn about how to train different models in
在这部分 我们学习如何训练不同的模型
以及如何调整参数 以便更好地训练我们的模型
a scale learn and how to play with parameters in order to train our model better.
As you can imagine, as the data gets bigger and more complicated,
可以想象出 随着数据集越庞大并且越复杂
this process of picking the right algorithm
选择正确算法和正确参数
and the right parameters can get pretty tedious.
这一流程会非常枯燥
In fact, there are many techniques that we can use to help us with these decisions.
实际上 有很多技巧可以帮助我们做出这些决策
This is what we learn in the rest of this section.
我们在这节课的后续阶段将学习这些技巧
How to train, test, evaluate,
如何训练 测试 评估和验证模型
and validate models in order to make the best decisions with our data.
以便针对我们的数据做出最佳决策